<rss version="2.0">
    <!-- Produced by the bleb.org TV system -->
    <!-- ([0-9]{2}<hour>)([0-9]{2}<minute>) : ([\w\s\d]+<title>) -->
    <channel>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        <title>bbc1 Listings</title>
        <item>
            <title>0600 : Breakfast</title>
            <description>The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team. Also in HD. [S]
                Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes past each hour.
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0915 : Council House Crackdown</title>
            <description>4/10. Reality series following housing fraud investigators. Here, they are joined by the police
                to reclaim a flat which is no longer occupied by the official tenant. Also in HD. [AD,S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1000 : Homes Under the Hammer</title>
            <description>Property renovation series. Will a terraced house in Croydon, a semi in the Welsh village of
                Maerdy and a former barber's shop in Sutton Coldfield prove to be good investments? Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1100 : Family Finders</title>
            <description>4/15. Documentary series. Three half-sisters who were placed separately into care and grew up
                unaware of each other's existence are finally reunited. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1145 : Break-in Britain - The Crackdown</title>
            <description>4/15. Caught on Camera: A look at burglaries in the UK. A brazen burglar uses his bicycle as a
                stepladder to break into the home of a blind man in Leeds. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1215 : Bargain Hunt</title>
            <description>Antiques challenge. The teams are in Sawbridgeworth, Herts, with experts Charlie Ross and
                Natasha Raskin. Tim Wonnacott finds a collection of unusual silver items. Also in HD. [AD,S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1300 : BBC News at One</title>
            <description>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather.
                Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1330 : BBC London News</title>
            <description>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]</description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1345 : Doctors</title>
            <description>Drama series set in a health centre. Ayesha grows concerned for patient Jenna, who seems to
                fall victim to a lot of mishaps which can't be easily explained. Also in HD. [AD,S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1415 : For What It's Worth</title>
            <description>4/23. Antiques quiz show hosted by Fern Britton. Antiques expert Anita Manning assists Fern as
                the three teams compete for the prize. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1500 : Escape to the Country</title>
            <description>Denise Nurse is property-shopping in rural Devon with one born-and-bred Londoner and her dog.
                While in the county, Denise heads to the coast to taste a unique crab variety. Also in HD. [AD,S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1545 : Chelsea Flower Show</title>
            <description>9/15. Nicki Chapman and James Wong take a celebratory look at the small gardens. Also in HD.
                [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1630 : Flog It!</title>
            <description>Antiques series. Paul Martin presents from Sandon Hall in Staffordshire, with experts Christina
                Trevanion and Charles Hanson. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1715 : Pointless</title>
            <description>Quiz in which contestants try to score as few points as possible by plumbing the depths of
                their general knowledge to come up with the answers no-one else can think of. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1800 : BBC News at Six</title>
            <description>The latest national and international news stories from the BBC News team, followed by weather.
                Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1830 : BBC London News</title>
            <description>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S]</description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1900 : The One Show</title>
            <description>If it's got Britain talking then it will get talked about on The One Show. Presented by Matt
                Baker and Alex Jones. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>1930 : EastEnders</title>
            <description>Ian reels from his latest discovery, and things continue to go downhill. Sharon turns to Linda
                for support. Also in HD. [AD,S] Then BBC News.
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2000 : How Should I Vote? - The EU Debate</title>
            <description>Live from Glasgow, Victoria Derbyshire hosts a debate on the issues that matter to younger
                voters ahead of the June referendum on whether or not Britain should remain in the EU. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2100 : The Truth About Alcohol</title>
            <description>A&amp;E doctor Javid Abdelmoneim is on a mission to find out the truth about alcohol, including
                why the government cut the recommended weekly limit for men by a third in January. Also in HD. [AD,S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2200 : BBC News at Ten</title>
            <description>The latest national and international news, with reports from BBC correspondents worldwide.
                Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2230 : BBC London News</title>
            <description>The latest news, sport and weather from London. [S] Followed by national weather.</description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2245 : Question Time</title>
            <description>David Dimbleby presents topical debate from Ipswich. On the panel are Ed Miliband, David Davis,
                Caroline Lucas, Dreda Say Mitchell and Steve Hilton. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2345 : This Week</title>
            <description>Andrew Neil reviews the political week with Nick Clegg, Michael Portillo and Jess Phillips on
                the big red sofas. Plus guests Francis Boulle, Helen Lewis and Brian Blessed. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0030 : Weather for the Week Ahead</title>
            <description>Detailed weather forecast. Also in HD. [S]</description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0035 : Joins BBC News</title>
            <description>BBC One joins the BBC's rolling news channel for a night of news, with bulletins on the hour
                and the headlines every 15 minutes. Also in HD. [S]
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>0600 : Breakfast</title>
            <description>The latest news, sport, business and weather from the BBC's Breakfast team. Also in HD. [S]
                Including regional news at 25 and 55 minutes past each hour.
            </description>
            <link>http://tv.bleb.org/</link>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
